CLARA KANG: WEB DEVELOPER

213-335-0214 | clara.kang91@gmail.com | clarakang.com | linkedin.com/in/clarakang | github.com/claarafy

SUMMARY

I'm a web developer with experience in marketing and mathematics educational background. A mathematical approach to web development helped me get a good grasp of the back-end development, and creativity in product decision and front-end UI experience. Currently, I'm working with MERN stack application project and developing my knowledge in React, as well as solidifying my foundation in the languages I learned.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML5 | CSS3 | JavaScript | jQuery | Ruby | Rails | Node.js | Express | React | ES6 | AJAX | Wordpress | SaSS | Bootstrap | P5 | PostgreSQL | mongoDB | Authentication with bcrypt/passport/jwt | Git/Github | Heroku

PROJECTS

NO LALA LAND May 2017

NO LALA LAND is a single-page map application that provides street parking information in vicinity of the queried location.

React with ES6 | Node.js | Express | MongoDB | HTML | CSS | Mapbox (3rd Party API)

Ctrl + F May 2017

Ctrl + F is a search engine application that allows both searching and reviewing on the specific result; users are able to see the search result with appended reviews on the website all in one space.

Node.js | Express | MongoDB | HTML | CSS | Bing (3rd Party API)

Until We Part April 2017

Until We Part is a photo-sharing web application for private groups, particularly built for families. Ruby on Rails | Bootstrap | HTML | CSS

U-B-U April 2017

U-B-U (You Be You) is a 2-player paper doll memory game with custom-drawn character. JavaScript | jQuery | CSS | HTML

EXPERIENCE

Marketing Manager, Tapzin Korea

February 2015 – August 2015

- Led a team of six to curate engaging magazine articles to create Tapzin's own contents. Targeted curation has resulted in 5% increase in monthly downloads as well as 2% growth of Monthly Active Users.
- Raised brand awareness by developing online campaigns on SNS channels, by communicating with the partners (magazine and media companies), for collaborative promotion projects and event coordination.

Accounting Assurance Intern, PwC Korea

June 2013 – August 2013

- Worked with a team of audits to conduct "test of detail," research, as well as evaluation of current conditions for the largest telecommunication company in Korea.

EDUCATION

Emory University August 2010 — May 2014

Bachelor of Arts(B.A.), Economics and Mathematics

General Assembly March 2017 — May 2017

Web Development Immersive: Front-end / Back-end Web Development